Let's get to work. Um, it's Friday,
September 11th, 25 years ago.
Uh,
I lost my best friend and the best man
at my wedding. Uh, tonight I am going to
go out with some other friends. So, I'm
going to talk about that briefly, but I
just wanted to uh say I'm thinking for
everyone that lost someone in in there
or remembers that day as something as
tragic as it was for me. Uh I uh thank
everyone for reaching out after I kind
of relayed that story a few weeks ago
when I was still in Maine. So we're
going to go through linear verse
exponential thinking. Uh oil bonds and
Fed. Oh my. I'll continue on this thing
of if you're paying attention to oil
bonds and the Fed, uh you're in a linear
world and you need to focus on AGI has
arrived. That should be the big news
story of the week. It shouldn't be
whether bond yields were up 10 basis
points, whether oil was up $10, whether
the Fed might goes from 65% to 85%. Uh,
AGI has arrived. Uh, I'm going to go
through Astra. I'm going to give you
guys some podcast to get up to speed. I
am going to show you how to build a
trading system using it and especially
for your kids. I created a subscriber
video uh this week after I built one
myself. I'm going to go through what I
did, what you guys can do, uh, how you
can attach an AI agent to it using Mumu,
Robin Hood, Interactive Brokers, you
three, reach out to me. I'm trying to
help your people be able to do what I'm
going to show and connect it in there so
that they can start building systems,
even if it's paper trading at this
point. The amount of entrepreneurial
success people will have by being able
to do this will blow them away. It will
empower them significantly. Of course,
there's bad news. Robin Hood, we'll go
through a question that I get asked all
the time, which is hard to answer for
people. How to value Ethereum and the
crypto ecosystem. So, uh, Christopher
Shawn Kaitton. Shawn Kaitton who worked
at Caner. I'm sure there's people that
over the years had, uh, met him. This is
a photo of him on a July 4th. Uh, very
big manquan person. And here is his name
down here. Tonight I will be going out
with these three guys. Um that's me.
This is almost 40 years ago now. That is
a photo of Shawn at my wedding.
Uh so again for people who remember this
day uh in the emotional way that I do I
am thinking about you linear visser
labs. Again you have to make a decision
which side of this you want to be on. If
you're worried about oil bonds and
rates, again, I'm going to keep saying
during these years, the economy cared
about oil bonds and rates. That all
changed beginning in 2008. That is when
the exponential world took off because
of the release of iPhone the year before
and because transfer payments started to
grow and the government really started
to take up its debt. This is when we
exited this point and this started and I
went to Silicon Valley in 2013. I'll get
through that again as I've talked about,
but this is the world we're in and this
is the world that has been making money
since 2008. You wanted to be in the MAG
7. So, I figured by now people would
have learned their lesson about caring
about where oil was, where rates were,
where all this stuff was, other than
again, I get it traders. But on a day
where we had higher than expected core
inflation yesterday, we had higher than
expected PPI, the probability the Fed
went up, crude oil went through, the war
is getting worse, and over the two days,
as of when I started doing this, the S&P
was up slightly. So, how do these things
actually matter if they don't matter? So
again, the news is focused on this. This
is a linear world. These are things that
mattered when housing and autos were
driving the economy. AI capex is driving
the economy. And as I showed last week,
it is not at all rate sensitive. Uh the
Fed rate hike odds surged to 90%.
Jackson Hole from Timuros. I think this
the reason I put this in there is the
market is testing you, Warsh. This is a
double dog daring you. This is straight
schoolyard. The market is fighting with
wars and bessent which I think is just
great because more importantly I think
people should be looking for ways to
make money on the linear on the
exponential side. But again that's just
me. That's why I'm doing these videos
because I think you guys are here either
to at least know what's happening in
that part of the world but also some of
you want to make money on it. Uh the
third mandate moderate long-term
interest rates for the Fed. Just always
keep this in mind that Trump clearly has
got Bessant to be fighting the market in
a way that Trump would fight the market
participants and Worsh isn't fighting
people but at the same time he was
chosen by Bessant and Trump and they
don't want rates higher. So we'll see
what happens. Uh Besson's upsized
buybacks get hit. So he goes to six
billion and the market immediately sells
off again. Good news hit with bad news.
So that means the market's acting badly,
but the S&P's up over the two days. Is
it talk time to talk about plan B? If
this doesn't work, they'll just cut
long-term issuance outright.
I mean, Besson is trying to be as
obnoxious as possible. Um, I am the
House now. Underscore his level of
engagement on economic policymaking in
Japan where he has coordinated with
Japan finance minister again why
fighting the government is the best
trade. He's speaking out against the
Bloomberg terminal bros. The arrogance
stuff is coming out for the week. The
S&P
we're holding the 50-day for now.
There's nothing much going on. Again,
this looks more like a flag formation
after a big high. We had this one here,
then we went sideways, then we went up
again. As I mentioned last week, we're
barely up since June 2nd. So unless the
economy is going to fall off and
earnings are going to fall off, as far
as I'm concerned, we can keep doing this
for a while. But if you look, we did
this rip and then pain here. We did this
rip and then pain here. Guys, I showed
this with Nvidia. Get used to the fact
that when this just rips, it's going to
rip for three days just when you're
feeling like it has no chance of
ripping.
Here are the facts. Revisions this week
32 up there. This is the 20week average
of revisions.
Here's PMI. The leading indicators are
doing great. HYG relative to IEF, the
proxy that I'll use real time and the
one that I care the most about as an
overlay rel instead of spreads. Two, the
S&P had a huge ripper week. HYG up
relative to EF, meaning as bonds are
selling off, HY is not. Here it is
overlaid with the S&P. If you go back
and look at this in 2022 when the Fed
was aggressively raising rate hikes as
the S&P was going down, this was going
down despite rates going higher. So
again, the proxy for the equity market
with credit completely fine. And as I
said last week, bond va's not moving,
junk spreads aren't moving. Uh any part
the inflation expectations via tips not
moving like the market is saying h we
don't really care about what's going on.
But the aida and the emotion in people
is AI thematic portfolio. My portfolio
uh breaking above the 50-day today.
We'll see if it can get going. Um we're
still doing the low V consolidation
here, but we've already broken the
50-day on what I consider the most
important part, which is my 10 name
concentrated one of the 10 names that I
feel are the best by different
groupings. So, if you guys haven't done
it yet, I'd go look at it because it
broke above the 50-day and it's getting
close to the August highs.
The names are all acting well. Bitcoin,
well,
flag
range trading, Ethereum
break, we'll see if it can continue.
Broke broke back in before today's
close. Uh, but again, I've said it
before, I think Ethereum should be
outperforming Bitcoin when we're
actually in the bull market. uh because
the ecosystem and the network effect
should be the critical thing because the
agentic side especially with Astra and a
huge week for Ethereum over Bitcoin
breaking out again to the highest level
since January.
Bessent warns nothing else would matter
if China wins the AI race. There is no
day after tomorrow if China wins this.
Why would we fight the AI trade and why
would you fight the bond side? Go with
what he's saying. you don't have to go
buy bonds because that to me is not a
good idea. But I do believe fighting the
AI trade is a bad idea. So again, do you
want to be a linear side of my V or do
you want to be the exponential side? You
guys make the choice. But again, this is
the big news of the week. We've talked
about AGI. We've heard about AGI. Jensen
Yuang, the godfather of AI, said AGI has
arrived with Astra.
The moonshot's portfolio covered it well
and again 100,000k
is what basically Astro was trained on.
The next model is four times the size
and behind that the Vera Rubins. Why
fade this guys? Why? Why? The IQ is
going through the roof and we're doing
things unthinkable. So it was trained on
100,000. They say research agents are
now generating 3.1 workdays for every
human workday. They hit the Navier
Stokes
challenge which mathematicians have been
trying to do for a long time by using
10,000 AI agents working in parallel for
88 hours. So we hear about the agents
working together on the negative side.
This is then solving some of the world's
greatest problems which have huge
implications for physics and as I'll
show huge implications for the PE of the
S&P 500 going up five years. Compute can
increasingly be converted into
intelligence. Intelligence can be
multiplied into thousands of agents. So
again, more compute, higher
intelligence, more intelligence, more
agents. We're at the critical point
where this is where we were in October
of last year. We reached the point of
high enough IQ to move into the second
side. Those agents can be put at
problems like the Navier Stokes which
get us closer to curing drug disease at
a mass scale solving problems for energy
solving all physics pro like we start
getting into the things that it's all
built on and that's where we are now the
agentic side means a big change and
that's why I talk about crypto so much
it's why I talk about other parts which
we'll go through but we need more
compute for that and we are nowhere in
the compute side so we need a lot of
GPUs and that's why GPU prices just
refuse to go down.
Now the way GDP changes more people plus
more capital plus higher productivity.
That's what the formula has always been
on. But with AI a new possibility shows
up. We have the human labor. Same thing
up here. We don't need more people
though because we now have digital labor
and we actually have accelerating
productivity because we not only have
more of these to replace these but as I
showed these work at three to five times
this. This is my whole if you just take
weekly hours, go through the economy for
human beings, you add in the lunch
breaks, the smoking breaks, the flirting
breaks, and everything else that goes on
and the daydreaming and not working.
Just go back to um the office and go see
how much time was wasted. Agents don't
do that. They have no need for that.
They also have no emotions from a
trading side, which I'll get through.
The old constraint on GDP was ultimately
the number of humans and the
productivity of their time. The new
constraint may increasingly become
compute, energy, and our ability to
deploy intelligence. The reality is GDP
productivity already is accelerating.
It's seen through profit margins at this
point. Forget the economist trying to
figure this out. The model of GDP is
wrong. You can't say that GDP, the index
created in the 1930s to measure
industrial production, is the right
metric to be using to say productivity
is not higher. Think about it.
Productivity is an output of GDP. GDP
doesn't count IP. G GDP doesn't count
lots of things. That's why we change it
all the time. It doesn't know what's
happening. Navier Stokes importance. I'm
not going to take you through all this.
The reason I wanted to show this is
because Navier Stokes, which I knew
nothing about until two days ago, but I
spent a lot of time, as I always do,
when I hear something that they say is
really important from a physics basis
because it gets us closer to
solving things in energy,
transportation, compute, manufacturing,
again, efficiency, medicine, climate,
and more. But more importantly, I've
talked about this, the PE of the market,
which is is not here, but I want you to
think about it. The economy gets bigger
because of science break breakthroughs.
So the total economic size gets bigger.
More energy, more transportation, more
compute, more manufacturing. Go spend
time on why that's the case. Again, we
get to a point where the TAM gets bigger
at the same time that corporate duration
gets shorter. This is terminal value. So
we've already gone through this episode
for
software companies. We're kind of going
through it already in hardware with
Nvidia trading at such a cheap PE.
Multiples are going to compress because
terminal value, the ability to know when
a company will have a cliff of their
earnings no longer growing. And that's
all it takes. Because once AI disrupts
your business and your earnings are no
longer growing, where should your
multiple be? Should it be one? Where
should it be if you're not growing
anymore? That'll be a question that's
going. And I know human beings won't
want to buy anything that's not growing.
So you're left in a situation that's
there. Now if they're not growing, the
only way they want it is the usefulness
of the community and things like that.
Again, it gets back into crypto. It gets
into a mindset change which is happening
with younger people. It's never going to
happen with older people, but older
people will get recycled with the newer
people. So this is something important
to think about because solving Navier
Stokes leads to the ability of having
and I'm just going to go through that.
You can read all the different parts of
what this means. I just want you to know
it means better turbines, better
aircraft, better cooling systems, better
ships, better reactors, better
batteries, industrial products, and
more. Things just get more efficient. It
changes everything. If you want to go
read more about the people who know
what's coming and then let their
economist translate into what's coming,
go to the economists who actually see
the data. Most economists have no idea
what models are coming up. The
anthropicus economists do. So go read
their economics team. I know everyone's
going to read the Goldman Sachs one. I
know everyone's going to read the Morgan
and Stanley one. I know everyone's going
to read all these different ones and
they're going to listen to the rate
forecast and they're going to go through
this and I'm arguing that none of that
matters because it's all linear thinking
and that is the truth from my side. The
truth Greg Brockman from OpenAI spoke.
He's a boring guy but if you want to go
listen to the interview it's only 20
some odd minutes 24 minutes to be exact.
On there he gives a description of what
Astra is. So Astra AGI is here. He talks
about it. I highlighted the different
things you can go. He describes OpenAI's
direction as merging chat. That is the
one that almost everyone uses at this
point with agents. Almost no one uses
this with desktop. Almost no one uses
this. Codeex, no tools, no applica. All
of this in one place. So you can now use
Astra in this way. So I've been talking
about the fact that Grockbot allows you
to use agents. Well, guess what?
It's not the same user face. It doesn't
look like a fun video game with your
little agents running around, but you
can use agents in this as they did. And
that's where this all changes. And I
will get into a little bit of this when
we get into a trading system side. Uh
image models, everything along those
lines in one system. This is the
critical point for you, for your
children, for everyone who wants to get
better, who wants to follow on the path
of me spending all of my time on AI,
wants to use it for work, wants to use
it to build things, wants to have an
entrepreneurial mindset, and wants to be
empowered. So, if you don't like your
job as an accountant, if you don't like
your job in any kind of knowledge work,
this is the point where you want to
start paying attention.
Greg Brockman, we're really trying to
empower the individual to make it so
that you can have superpowers, you can
accomplish more. And I think that really
trying to benefit people, empower
people, build tools that can really help
you in your daily life. That's what this
thing does. So I did this on the video
series. So for those of you who are
subscribers who've never watched the
video series, if you have access to it,
um I did a five six-part video series
which is all about develop developing an
AI entrepreneurial mindset. For those of
you who are not subscribers, this is
where I would start is I would get these
and basically be in the position and
have your kids go through it. I think
this is critical especially for 15 year
olds and above. Let's say 15 to 24. I
also think it's very important for
people that don't like their jobs at
this point. But anyone who wants to
develop a new mindset to ask, to find,
to build, to test, to fail, to learn, to
adapt, to repeat. This is all what I'm
going to show you in the new video,
which is about how to build something
from scratch and use the tools without
needing any coding. I did 90% of the
work for the first save, if not 100% of
the work, but 90 plus% of the work and
AI can do the rest. Um, and I talk about
that in the video. It's an hour and a
half video. It does a combination of
walk you through slides to explain what
I'm doing and then go to the place where
the prompts all the prompts you're going
to get all it's 14 different prompts you
will have this thing and you're just
opening something that I built that I
saved on GitHub. So this will bring
empowerment you will feel a sense the
same way I did when I started to use AI
in a really big way with code two years
ago. I immediately felt like I had a
superpower. It gave me agency to build
my own business which is what I started
guys. So the YouTube and all of that
came after I took Python and after I was
able to manipulate AI in a way through
very basic stuff but know that the
models were going to get better to where
verbally I could just say this and I
didn't need to speak as I like to say in
the video. Coding to me was Chinese. I
could not understand it and so I had to
have other people translate for me. I
don't need that anymore and it leads to
entrepreneurship and you want to be an
entrepreneur right now because of that
duration of corporate moes that I
mentioned. If you work for a company
that company will be in trouble. So I
would say the majority of you work for
companies that need to fire people not
because hey we're using AI and our
business is thriving. They need to fire
people because they're under pressure.
And they're under pressure because AI
can do these things all the time. And I
know that because I'm doing it that way.
Astra is the most dangerous AI model
right now. I'm getting into something
here. These came out and this is what
triggered me on a journey on Monday,
Labor Day of this week. Yes, Labor Day
on a holiday. I was going through, I
just worked out and I started on the way
back, I saw all these things and I
immediately went back and said, "Whoa, I
want to build some alpha strategies.
This is cool." Now, I've built alpha
strategies before, but when I read
through these, this was completely
different. And so I uploaded these, got
the explanation, I uploaded this, I
uploaded this Jane Street intern openly
shows on Reddit, but all of this stuff
to me, got uploaded into chat GPT. And
you'll be shocked if you just take my
computer screen, take your snipping
tool, if you're on a uh a ThinkPad or a
Microsoft thing, you know that think
that snipping tool. If you don't, just
go in search snipping tool, take a a
snapshot of it, and then go stick it
into chat GPT and say, "Can you rebuild
this?" Now, if you don't have Astra,
it's not going to work the same way.
Astra is part of the bigger package, but
I think most people at this point have
some access to it. If you don't, you can
find out how to get access to it. Astra
ran six AI agents on my trading account.
Probe was one of them. Prism was one of
them. Again, this is why I said this is
basically the same thing as
Grock. I put $500 in, $5,100 in the pot
by the morning. Now, I could care less
about these back tests and people making
money. I don't care. And that's one of
the things I go through. The great thing
about a back test is it should fail most
of the time. And to build an AI trading
desk,
the system is designed to reject almost
everything. This is what I love most
about this
ideas
found. So, thousands of ideas every day.
This is the critical way to getting to
something that works is the filtering
process. Look at it. Many many ideas 99%
rejected.
The the balance of the 1% makes it
there. Then it gets 90% of those get
rejected. By the time you get to the
end,
you have models. Now again, if you're
wondering how, let's say this here is
Millennium
deciding, and I saw this firsthand with
my hedge fund or the hedge fund that I
worked at that closed down. Okay, we
like this, we don't like this, we want
this, we don't want this. They go
through and they're looking at ideas and
they're looking at data to support it.
It's some back test because they can't
see the actual people and what went on
on a daily basis. They can get daily
returns, but they don't see what
responded, what happened in their space,
whatever the case. They're just trying
to minimize the chance. So, they have
their own process. Everyone who's
figuring out who to hire people to get
returns has it there. If you use AI and
then you get one and you get two and you
get three and you get four and you
combine them all together and they're
all uncorrelated, you're basically
creating a mini multistrat. So, again,
for anyone who wants to build not only a
trading desk, but wants to build a
system,
you can do that. You really can because
the agents can replace the humans on the
trading side and I'm telling you the
lack of emotion will be better. They
will develop the skill set that's there.
I believe for most human beings like I
showed that V where everything changed
as of the great financial crisis. We're
at another kind of point of the
exponential cycle. So what you learned
over the past 10 years is not going to
be as helpful as responding today.
That's why I think momentum becomes a
dominant factor and why I wanted to go
do something my own. So one of the edges
that I still think human beings have is
on those ideas side
what I did is wanted to build a
technical system of when to buy things
with inside the thematic portfolio. So
for those of you who've asked for these
things who've looked for trading signals
who take the technical side with all of
the data I give you and then want to
look at the ratings and be like well
this thing said buy. No thing doesn't
tell you what to do. Yes, it'll give you
some number of what it believes is a buy
signal without any kind of a really deep
algorithm. What I wanted to do is go
back test things and just say okay based
on what has happened over the past 5
years, 10 years, nine years, what's in
trend, what's resetting. So I created
what is basically out of trend resetting
coiled trending structural trend sign
and this is all based on my belief of
what's happening in the market. So, I've
talked to you guys about market
structure changing. I've had lots of
conversations with the biggest mutual
funds and hedge funds in the world about
this. They seem very interested in how
market structure is changing. They don't
know why in their head, but they
understand that it is changing because
it's getting harder to make money in a
consistent way without getting out of
stuff ahead of time. So, it's making it
more challenging because I believe
what's going on is you're later to
things then they get so far overbought
they make perfect sense and like I did
with the AI trade. I used what had
happened because I believe the critical
thing is select the hundred stock
universe. So, take my hundred names. I
believe those hundred names are going to
benefit from the AI buildout over the
next five years. The infrastructure
needs, the compute needs, that is a
capex trade. Those are the names that
are going to benefit. Now, I think most
of them will do what they've done. 80
plus% are above the 200 day moving
average with their 200 day moving
average pointed upward. Great. I think
overall that's going to create alpha.
That's a structural bull market. I don't
think you're going to get what you saw
in the first quarter again. So, like
I've said before, I don't think people
should expect Micron to go back to to do
a 5,000 from here over the next year,
another five bagger. Do I think uh
2,000's possible, 1,800, 1,700? Let's
say 1,600. We're at a,000 right now. you
wouldn't take 60% on the name even
though it was a 12 bagger before. Um, I
think it's going to be really hard to
find those names because like I said,
multiple compressions coming. So, I
think it's great that the multiples are
compressing for Nvidia and Micron. I
just don't think you're going to be able
to make money on them the oldfashioned
way of being in there and they go up all
the time. I think most days they'll be
either down or flat. Uh, and at the end
of the year, maybe 5% of the rally, the
days will be the rallies you need to
miss. And if you miss those five days,
you miss the whole move. So what I did
is I said rate of change matters. What I
care about is the structural uptrend and
then I'm looking for a resetting. This
is what the midcycle slowdown was. This
is when I got out of micron way before
the top. Then after that's happened I
want to see coiled on deck. Now to do
that I used ATR. That's what started
this whole thing. Average true range
which I've talked about. Um it's part
it's a major part of the model. So's
rate of change get coiled. Then there's
an ignition. What's the initial point?
what treats a breakout and then we're
trending again. So, I'm looking for
structural bull markets. When things get
overdone, I want to basically be out
based on rate of change and then I want
to wait for them to reset. And I'm
looking constantly for ideas within the
space that way. I think you guys are
going to enjoy it. This is the theory
behind it. I'm not going to read you
guys because it's just resetting some of
the things I said,
but the back test looks great. So, I'm
I'm going to give you the end result
signals on that. At the same time,
I did a subscriber video. Like I said,
it's basically on the theme of a
treasure hunt. Uh, this is everything
that comes in it. So, you know, you're
going to get code, you're going to get
prompts, you're going to get a research
log, tools, this because it's all on
GitHub. I put the whole thing in GitHub.
Yes, you guys don't know what GitHub is.
I'm going to show you in a second. I
also built in Socrates mode for you. So,
again, this is what you're going to be
able to do. So, subscribers who are at
this level, you're going to get access
to it. use it. Here's what GitHub is. If
you don't know, and I use that Chinese
analogy for my life having data
scientists, I needed them to basically
be able to go into GitHub, which is a
library of code. So, you don't have to
reinvent the wheel. I go through this
and show you how you can go in there and
if you're an accountant, show me aic
code accounting so I can be get
superpowers in accounting so I can
develop my own skill of knowing how to
use a AI to be able to do more
accounting work for my company without
needing to lose my job. How do I use AI
to do this? How do I help them? All of
these things or how do I go set up my
own business? Whatever. But this gives
you coding in so many different things.
It is not just the finance side, but I
use the finance because back testing
something I think everyone wants.
Everyone wants a treasure hunt. They
want to think that they've created
renaissance. They've created all this
stuff. And believe it or not, guys, you
can have a trading system that can make
you money going through the thing that
you do. And you can keep coming up with
new eyes, new ideas, new ideas, new
ideas by listen to Stan Duck Miller. Go
read a book on a chartered technic
technical analysis. Use Demark. I don't
really care. Whatever it is, go listen
to someone who's made money over time
and take the little parts they want and
create your own strategy. You can make
money in it. And again, it may not be
scalable to run it at a multistrat in
big size with a billion dollars, but
there's plenty of strategies that you
can do. And I believe AI can continue to
find new strategies at small levels.
This is one of the things with
tokenization. You can do crypto as well.
So, as long as you have good data, you
can go through it. So, it starts with a
question. We go to GitHub. We had our
own idea. We test it, tried to break it.
This is actually what happened in the
video. And then we learned how to fail.
And this is the golden side. You're
basically learning how to fail and then
restart and go through it again. When
you find one that works, this shows you
all the ways to kind of go through the
promise, go through the progress using
AI. It will take you through so many
levels that are hard to do or hard to
learn on your own. So, I think you guys
will enjoy it. I uploaded it this week.
Again, for people at Robin Hood, for
people at Mumu, for people at
Interactive Brokers, this will allow
people to do what I have here, come up
with their own trading system, and then
they can upload it, and you guys can
show them how it can be an agentic
trading system on a paper trade. So,
they can see if it works for whatever
period they want. They can then upload
10 more. And that way, they're
increasing the probability. If you have
10 different ones running at the same
time with $100 in each or $50 in each,
well, now you've got kind of a little
mini multistrat of different strategies
going on at the same time, you're
starting to get empowered and you're
starting to build something. And more
importantly, your brain will start
changing because you're developing an
entrepreneurial mindset. So again,
you'll see
me as a pirate in the video. This is a
different version. Um, but again, this
is what it's going to take you through.
This is where the Robin Hood Mumu, if
you haven't seen it, again, these
companies offer a Gentic side. So, I
know the people at Mumu. I've already
spoken to them. I want to find ways to
get you guys to get empowered on this
and do this stuff on your own. Here's
the Aentic trading set from Robin Hood.
Mumu launches Agentic Investing. They've
been doing this really since April 23rd,
but I had a meeting with them last week.
continue to be more advanced on this in
my opinion in terms of trying to do this
allowing paper trading going through it
giving you the API the data prices so as
long as you go in and open an account
with them you're going to have access to
their data so you don't need to use
Yahoo Finance and their data they're
telling me is far better than Yahoo
Finance you guys can go see on your own
and of course Interactive Brokers has
had this for some time too this is as of
June of 2026 so you will learn you will
build you advance and then you can plug
it into a trading platform. It's pretty
cool. I'm doing it with my stuff and
hopefully I'll be able to give you guys
a a look at this in the way that they
have it from the paper trading side. So,
I'm not going to end with this. I will
show this for you guys. And again, find
a GitHub code project that exists that
could help an accountant begin to
incorporate AI, how to do their job.
First, let me know how many you find. I
found at least 13 relevant GitHub
projects that could help an accountant
start incorporating AI into real-time
accounting flows. A few of them are
particularly strong for the message
you're building. You don't have to wait
for someone to build AI for accountants.
It's already being built on a public
GitHub. So again, don't be an AI victim.
Find, build, experiment, learn. Everyone
can do this. If you're young and you
just started at an accounting firm, I'm
telling you, spend the time on the
weekend going through this and then see
if they will let you use it. At a
minimum, you will know where everything
is going. Sundar Pachai, if you don't
learn how to orchestrate agents now,
you'll spend 2027 catching up to people
who started today. That is the truth.
Microsoft plans data center pushed
triple its computing power. I remember
people were saying the AI trade was the
reason it petered out was because
Microsoft's I mean this just never
stops. Demand for Astra is really
unprecedented. 6.2 million views.
They're running out of space for it
already. Now, this is an important one.
These are the H100s.
And I just want to take you back to the
Michael Burries, the Jim Chanos's, and
all the people that said on the
accounting side, this is the thing
you'll never get. So for all those guys
that said this depreciation is a risk
and the reason it's a risk is because
there's no chance the those
prices will go higher. You have to
depreciate those. And saying this is
going to last for more than three years
is ridiculous, especially when the
technology is getting so much better.
The technology is getting better.
Reubens are far better than the H100s.
H100 rental prices are almost at the
same level as they were three years ago.
Think about that, guys. They're at the
same price. We weren't talking about
them making it for six years. We were
talking about Yeah. How can you build in
They're unchanged in three years. So,
this again gets into the fact that the
demand is insatiable. I'll say it every
single time. By now, there's a normal
aging process of chips. They should at
least be down whatever say 10%. They're
unchanged maybe 20%. The normal rate of
what people would have thought is down I
don't know 40% 50% by this time in three
years and they're almost the same level
and scarily they've actually gone
higher. Every depreciation scale assume
assumes a chip to sold lose only loses
value. The market is playing paying up
for it instead. So its rental price is
up 22% on the month.
I take you back to Gavin Baker one month
ago.
His core point was that the market was
assuming GPU rental prices would
steadily fall. Again, this was a month
ago. You see what it's doing this month.
Instead, older GPUs were holding their
value far better than expected. In some
cases, rental prices were actually
rising. Exactly what we just saw. What
he said was, and this is the critical
point, this changes the financing
debate. So this is about how much debt
the hyperscalers will need. The cash
flow estimates for the hyperscalers in
cloud in his opinion are way too low
because of this situation. If cloud
providers generate much more cash from
repricing their existing compute. So
again, think of this side as you buy
tomatoes at $2
and the ability to sell tomatoes has now
gone up to $20. That is the compute
side. So the compute side is using these
GPUs to what you can sell to people
because the demand for the end compute
is so large when it comes out of the
data center that the chips that were
bought to go in the data center have not
had their prices fall yet. So the
margins get really really high because
what they get to do is repric the
compute when the contracts end. So if
they if they bought these at $2 and
let's say the compute was at $3 and now
compute prices are at $6, but they're
still using and the demand for the $2
ones is still there based on the fact
that people were willing to pay $3 for
them. So they get to reset their compute
which was set at $3 to $6. This could
remove hundreds of billions of dollars
of expected credit needs. So again,
whether or not you agree with it, the
market is depreciating GPUs, the rental
market is not, that's the issue. And so
when you look at Nvidia and you look at
the hyperscalers, there is a way that
this can turn into not needing as much
credit and free cash flow going up. And
like I've said before, they have
tremendous amounts of not only demand,
they have cap they they have a capacity
shortage and Microsoft just reiterated
that this week. Now, Paul Tudtor Jones
put out a, you know, a negative piece on
AI. This is not the first time he's gone
through it, and this is not a negative
pace on the technology. He and I have
exchanged emails, uh, over the past
month. I think his, you know, he's
legitimately
engaged with people trying to figure out
what's going on. And what's happening is
shocking. And again, that's how fast
things are moving. Greg Jensen warned AI
may need to kill people before
regulation is kickstarted. If you didn't
see Iranian hackers shut down a UK power
plant. Boston Scientific striker drop on
fallout from cyber attacks. So the cyber
attacks were so bad for Boston
Scientific that they had to reduce their
earnings forecast. Anthropic discloses
the fourth AI hacking incident involving
Opus 4.6.
Anthropic says Iran used its American AI
model to target US Navy warships. So,
this is not all positive on AI and I
believe that this hacking situation will
continue. It's one of the reasons why
I'm very positive on crypto as well
because I think AI leads to not trusting
anything and it will not stop the
earnings. It will not stock
productivity, but it will hurt smaller
businesses and smaller companies that
can't protect themselves. So, the cyber
side is increasing dramatically. I've
heard personally many many places uh
through conversations about hit uh about
hackings in bitcoin related wallets and
all kinds of things uh not on the chain
so the chain is safe but the apps that
are on top for everything have become an
issue now way put this out again we're
starting to see the AI adopters again
earnings grow so I think you're going to
keep saying the profit margins go higher
and again I showed this last week I'm
going to say it Again, the market has
never been cheaper or at least in the
last 30 plus years with the PEG ratio
down here. So, everyone who's negative
goes, "Yeah, but this is peak uh
earnings." Well, revisions are still
going higher and we haven't even got to
a point yet where this is falling and
profit margins usually start to come
over first. So, we're It's not like
we're getting anywhere on this. If
profit margins are going higher, guys, I
don't know how if expenses don't need to
go higher. I I like again we're at the
productivity boom point. So I wrote this
paper this week. We're going to move
into the crypto section again very soon.
You guys are seeing this now. About 30%
is now crypto because this is in a bull
market and this is where I want to focus
my attention. So I wrote this on what I
believe is the most important conversion
in the world. The Robin Hood convergent.
Robin Hood is basically the epicenter of
AI
crypto macro nexus. It is a trady
company that has been somewhat involved
in crypto but not making a ton of money
on it relative to its other businesses.
And it's an agentic company. So you guys
should read this for the subscribers who
got it. Uh and for the institutions that
are getting this uh but won't be at some
point soon unless you're subscribers.
Um, again, I'm starting to go through
this in in a very big way, and you
should go read about Robin Hood because
it is your entree into understanding how
to start thinking about it from an
earnings perspective. The chain is now
earnings. Bernstein sees 31% upset for
Robin Hood as fees top Salana.
Robin Hood chain fees record 6 million
in daily fees. Robin Hood chain has only
been live for two months and it's
already starting to rerate the onchain
market. Arbitum, which is basically the
app on top of it, surges 7.87% on Robin
Hood chain. Boom. Uh, Arbitron. What are
they? Oh, see, here's the news. You can
go see it. Now, if you want to go see if
Tradfi is covering it, Arbitron Wall
Street Journal did not match any news
results. Shocking. You're not going to
learn anything from anyone unless you
come to me uh from the Trady
perspective. You can go to CoinDesk. You
can go to crypto which are great places
for this but I'm looking at it from the
angle of merging the three of them tradi
plus AI plus crypto which I think is
critical especially for Robin Hood the
AI agent site is the most important side
uh if you didn't see they strike a deal
with crypto.com the merge is continuing
you want to be long stuff that looks
like this is the pers like I said last
week if you don't know what pers are
please go pay attention tokenized stocks
we continue to move forward on this.
Robin Hood spoke at the Goldman Sachs
technology conference
and here's the five big takeaways.
Aentic trading is going mainstream. This
is from Robin Hood. So this is from
Vlad, a hedge fund in your pocket. Well,
I'm showing you guys how to do that.
Robin Hood chain is about global
financial infrastructure. Yes, it is
tokenization.
I believe if you have an advantage, if
you get into tokenization ahead of
everyone on the Trady side as they start
to jump into this, which they will
because they will need to make alpha,
you're getting in front of the hordes of
money if the Clarity Act goes through.
And it's not a given that it won't go
through and I'll be in DC in two weeks.
I'm hopeful that by then they've already
solved this, but
the Clarity Act has huge implications
from a spike perspective for this and
from an institution of credibility with
pension funds and things like that. So
there's catalysts coming up. Robin Hood
wants the entire financial relationship.
Trading, crypto, retirement, banking.
This is really critical, guys.
Prediction markets are a gateway
product. The bigger message. Robin Hood
is evolving from a brokerage app to AI
native tokenized financial platform
bringing it sounds a lot like Apple to
me. NASDAQ invests 100 million in
Kraken, eyeing the 2027 launch of
tokenized stock trading. Everyone's
preparing. US Bank test stable coins.
Visa stable coin card business is
exploding. European banks plan to launch
a euro stable coin on Ethereum. This is
all this week, guys. Coinbase says clear
US crypto rules are coming with or
without Senate approval. Brian Armstrong
said the Clarity Act is ready to get a
yes vote. Patrick Wit said the same
thing. The probabilities for this year
of getting it through are still below
20%. But that doesn't mean they can't
get a yes vote. So, this is where I'm
going to bring you to the final part.
William
Mogayier
gave a TED talk. I think this was 2014,
2015, could be 2016.
Um, no, no offense to William or Bill.
He's very boring. I love finding boring,
smart people. Um, because that means
people don't listen to him. I highly
recommend everyone goes listen this in
TED talks. It's as usual 17 minutes.
This is again a decade ago. him talking
about Ethereum and the important of
Ethereum and the importance of the
blockchain.
He did this a long time ago. Give me an
assessment on how correct his vision was
in what's happening today. He was 8 to
10 on direction but closer to 510 on
specific information which I think both
of those is good to get something
especially when when crypto has had so
much regulatory problems to actually
have an ability of guessing where things
were going to be and to get an eight out
of 10 on direction, five out of 10 on
specific is still good. where he was too
aggressive was removing the intermediary
and this is Robin is a perfect example.
I think this is the way to go through
it. He didn't know about stable coins.
The biggest thing he didn't see was AI
agents and this ironically they may
finally make his thesis work. That's the
whole point. When you listen to this, I
want you to connect AI agents to it.
This is the way I bring you guys alpha.
This is the way that you learn about
this and you get the connection of AI
agents because everything that he said
was assuming humans would use this. It's
not for humans.
This is what his original vision was. He
was a peer-to-peer guy. He was a Napster
guy. He talks at item. I'm going to go
through some other things because he
gives the best talk on valuation for
crypto. And I've been asked by so many
people inside and outside of crypto how
to value it. What happened instead? said
the middleman stayed in but AI and
crypto merge is changing it. So the AI
side is different from this. It is
critical for the success. It speeds
things up. So here's the other one. This
is now about 10 months ago. Ethereum's
endgame.
How to value Ethereum.
He talks about his experience in the
1990s and that's critical to this. Now,
I don't know a lot of tech people from
the 1990s who are still involved in the
market. They either made too much money,
they blew up, and they moved to
something else. It's been a young
person's game since the iPhone came in
for the most part. But there are people
that were around. And his point is, we
don't know how we we don't know how to
value Ethereum. It's a new model the
same way there was a new model when we
had to figure out how to value the
internet. And at first, it was eyeballs.
Had nothing to do with earnings.
This will get into my experience with
Amazon as we go through. Then revenue
finally started to matter in here. Then
SAS metrics came, but that's a long
time. That's 25 years before the metrics
came up. There was no SAS metrics. And
that's his point. So here they are.
Now it's about other things. So with
Ethereum and for all of crypto, there
will be revenue. There are network
effects. There's flow of money. And this
is what I talk about all the time.
There's ecosystem value, there's
productive assets, there's so many
things and it's programmable. You have
to go listen to this both podcasts. Just
listen to it. If you don't believe at
that point, it's fine. But then I want
you to go back to Amazon
in 1997 when it was a lowly online
bookstore to where it is now. Not now.
This is 2013. The reason I'll tell you
why I put this up there. So from here to
here,
27,000%
Ethereum right now from its lows is up
about 3,000%.
I really do believe we're going to see a
similar number at a similar time where
someone who's in Tradfi is finally going
to give up and say, "I don't understand
how to value this thing." I didn't
understand how to value Amazon at this
point. I was a macro person focused on
oil. I had made most of my money trading
on being either bearish or bullish oil
being bearish or bullish Brazil, China,
whatever. That was the places that I
made money. My best year was 2008 and
that was being short the US financial
system being what I was called as a
perma bear and being along emerging
markets and along commodities in a super
cycle.
I didn't understand this. And so when
this went back during the great
financial crisis, I figured for sure
this would go to zero because it didn't
make money. Well, it not only didn't,
but it came back faster. And when it
broke out, every single time it looked
head and shoulders, I can remember this
one. I showed it recently. It was
breaking down during the EU crisis. Went
right back up. Guys, its PE never ever
was below 100. It didn't even have a PE
for most of this. So, I went out to
Silicon Valley and say, "How can this
work?" I went to Singularity University.
That's when exponential started for me.
That's when my mind changed. That is 12
years ago. That is why I can talk about
crypto. That's why I'm using AI because
I know you're fading the inevitable.
When did Amazon finally reach a point of
having a PE
Tada. Below 100 for at least two
quarters.
Not till 2017, 2018. It wasn't until
2018 that it finally broke below for two
quarters in a row. Again, most of the
time before that, it didn't even have
earnings. You had to measure it on
eyeballs. Yes, truthful. So, when you're
trying to figure out how to value crypto
by the time it gets to the point where
it's no longer a ridiculous price,
you've already lost 27,000%
in 2013. I never wanted to make that
mistake again. For you mutual fund
people, for you people on the hedge fund
world, don't make the same mistake with
crypto if you still want to be involved
in markets from a bull market
perspective. That's my take on the
situation. He wrote a he has a new book
coming out, Trust Shift. I believe trust
is worth a significant amount of money
and I believe Ethereum is the trust
model. So you guys can just go through
it if you listen to his two things. Love
to hear from you, but I would do that.
AI makes trust an economic asset. I'm
100% sure that the blockchain needs
every real world asset to go on there to
keep its value. Trust is becoming an
issue. It is absolutely something to
measure things on. And anyone who wants
trust, it's going to have to go on
Ethereum. It has to final two slides. I
will be in DC. This is the presentation
I'm giving to a variety of people in DC,
not just crypto people, congressmen, the
whole thing. The time mismatch. So if
you want to join me, Freedom Tech DC
2026, September 23rd, 22nd, and 23rd, I
will be down there Monday night, Tuesday
night, Wednesday night, coming back
Thursday. Happy to meet up with people
that are there in DC if I have the time.
The Bitcoin Policy Institute's been
great on this. I will be a pub key with
them. This is one of the slides I will
be showing which again this is
tokenization. This is the bridge between
the digital world over here and again
the linear V, the exponential V, the
linear V. If you want to stay over here,
it's great. But this tokenized world is
coming. You're going to cross the bridge
at some point. Why not take a little
mini jump over here and start spending
your time here? And the Wall Street
Journal had Bitcoin's overlooked
promise, freedom. Again, for everyone
who lost someone or was affected by 911.
Uh, I'm thinking of you. It's a 24 25
year anniversary
of an emotional day for me. It tires me
whenever this day comes up to think
about. I am grateful for knowing Shawn
and I'm grateful for you guys watching
me every week. Uh, hit the subscribe
button, reach out, do whatever, but most
importantly, hug the ones you love today
and I'll see you guys next week.